theoutdoorstrader.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | The Outdoors Trader

The Outdoors Trader has established this privacy policy to explain how your information is protected, collected and used. This policy may be updated or otherwise modified, check it often.

The Outdoors Trader has a strict no spam policy. We may occasionally email useful information to our users, but we are very careful not to abuse that privilege and allow users to opt-out at any time.

## Protecting your privacy

We do not spam our users.

We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.

We offer relay email service, to reduce 3rd party harvesting & spam, your email is not made public.

## Data we collect

We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc.

We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback, comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on The Outdoors Trader that you expect to keep private.

Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, browser information, and timestamp. This information is used to diagnose problems, to administer the site, and otherwise provide service to you.

## Data we store

All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "de-activation," and may be archived elsewhere.

Our web logs and other records may be stored indefinitely.

Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

## Archiving and display of The Outdoors Trader postings by search engines and other sites

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with The Outdoors Trader archive or otherwise make available The Outdoors Trader postings.

## Circumstances in which The Outdoors Trader may release information

The Outdoors Trader may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

The Outdoors Trader may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of The Outdoors Trader, its users or the general public.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
